so how do you get your first coaching
client maybe you're like I want to build
this coaching business to six figures
and I don't know where to start that's
what I want to talk about in this video
is where to start and how to make sure
that you actually have paid clients not
just people that are using your time for
free but actually are paying you money
to work with you now for those of you
that I haven't met yet my name is
Jeremiah Kowski and for the last 21
years I have been helping mentors
trainers and coaches scale their
businesses to tens of Millions and I
built multiple coaching businesses over
$10 million per year and what I do is I
help beginners as well as those that
have been doing it a long time get more
clients scale their business and start
to make the kind of money that they want
to make six figures and eventually seven
figures we have proven processes and
systems as well as practical strategies
to help you get results and that's what
this YouTube channel is all about that's
what my content is all about we have a
podcast as well you can check out and I
have a coaching program where I actually
help you come alongside you and build
with you you actually get access to me
to help you build your business with you
all that to say I want to help you get
your first client that's what this video
is going to be all about okay you have
to know who your first client is going
to be it always starts with that making
a decision as far as who you want to
work with now we have other videos that
I've posted on this channel about
finding your Niche you can go search
that look up Jeremiah Kowski Niche and
you'll find some of those great videos
that we' put together I'm not going to
give a whole video Spiel on finding your
Niche on this what I want to talk about
is actually getting that client once
you've decided who you want to work with
that's the first stage how do we
actually get a client and it all boils
down
to conversations now don't log off the
video before you think I'm talking about
direct messages or one-on-one sales
calls okay because that's I don't
actually use any of those in my business
but we do facilitate conversation
ations in a way that does not require
you to work hundreds of hours or hire a
bunch of Staff or do complex methods and
how can you show up to have a
conversation with
somebody without actually having to take
your time to do so well let me give you
just a bird's eye example this video
right here is a form of a
conversation now you might be like H I
explain that I'm watching you we're not
talking back and forth but here's the
thing the thoughts that you're having
the ideas that you're having the things
that you're thinking while you watch a
video like this is an internal dialogue
that you're having with yourself while
you watch a training like this a piece
of content now here's the other thing
too you don't have to get on the content
creation hamster wheel when you use our
system you can actually find
strategically exactly what to do exactly
what steps to take that get results that
only have to take you 5 to 10 hours a
week and that's about how much I work as
well that's how much much I recommend
people work when they get started and it
happens when you facilitate
conversations that lead
to connection so we have to make sure
that we are
connecting with people that would be
potential clients when it comes to a
coaching relationship it's a it's it's a
bit deeper than just a business
transactional interaction if you ever
had a coach you know that it goes much
deeper than just that you have to Vibe
with the person right you have to make
sure that you like how they they do
things and number one what's the most
important thing that they can
deliver results because how many of
y'all are just tired of working with
coaches and mentors that don't actually
deliver on the things that they say that
they're going to deliver on and maybe
you might be here right now saying gosh
Jeremiah I don't know if I can deliver
on the results and that's why I'm
struggling to make connections with
people we'll stick with me I'm going to
help you with that as well in this video
okay when you can learn how to converse
with people in a way that gets them to
want to spend time with you and that's
one of the keys is you tap into one of
the deepest
drivers of getting clients which is
whoopsie that was
cute their desire okay leading with
desire desire and how many of y'all are
tired of traditional marketing that's
all pain and negativity driven right
here okay this gets your mind thinking
in a negative way and what I say is
let's
eliminate the pain points let's
eliminate what the struggle is and get
people off of the struggle train and
into a desire based state of mind now
everybody that's out there that might be
a potential client of yours has a dream
desire and they might sit up at night
and fantasize about the life they want
to live and that's great and you want to
tap into that in how you get clients
because if you want to figure out is
what do you help people with and again
we're going to be talking about how do
you deliver those results by the end of
this video but then how does that
correlate to the desire that somebody
actually has the reason why people make
a purchase with your coaching with your
offers to work with you in a business is
because you are delivering a desire one
of the biggest mistakes that people make
when it comes to getting
clients is they're not owning the
outcome that they're actually delivering
and that desire and they're timid and
they're passive and they're tiptoeing on
eggshells when they're communicating
even when they record video content or
trainings they're not showing up in
their great greatest
energy not in a new age sense but that
they're excited that they're actually
into and love what they get to do you
can see right now as you listen to me
I'm passionate about what I get to do
I'm excited about this I enjoy getting
results for my
clients and the biggest thing that
lights me up next to my wife and my sons
is getting my clients results and so
when you can show up and demonstrate
that to
people people will want to work with you
they
will essentially bang down your doors to
come in to work with you now not in a
weird sense but in the fact that they
will be like how can I work with you how
can I come and become a client of yours
and they will show up in droves to want
to be around you because you end up
creating an environment that people feel
seen
heard and that they want to spend time
in now getting people to want to spend
time inside of environment is cool and
all but that doesn't create results for
people but it is what gets you a client
and that's one of the things that I want
to help you is to separate these two
ideas in your mind okay this is one of
the most important things that if you
can get this this will help you is you
have the results driven side of delivery
this is how you're Del delivering the
results to your clients and we're going
to be talking about that by the end of
this video here but I want to lead it
with the
marketing and how do we tap into the
desire that people have to build trust
with them because before somebody is
willing to work with you to get these
results they have to trust that you are
going to deliver that desire to them so
your goal is to build trust with people
for people to say
okay I get what you're saying because
here's the thing you're not the only
coach that's out there news flash for
you we don't live under a rock we know
that there's other coaches mentors
course creators people and the industry
is more and more bombarded with offers
today than it ever has
been so how do you show up and stand out
with something that's marketable that
actually want to say okay I'm going to
work with you and not a
competitor that shows up in how you make
people feel first off because everybody
makes a buying decision based on
emotions and
feelings and how do you help people feel
that it's in a combination of your body
language the tone of
voice how happy or sad or how and how
you show up when you you communicate and
that's why video content is the most
effective way to actually get clients
whether it be on a zoom meeting or it be
face to face which I don't do anything
face to face anymore I do it all online
that's because I've designed my life
that way to live I I do face to face
with my friends and family but not with
clients as far as that goes I do face
Toof face over video online with
people and what that does is I've
learned how to make a connection with
people with the body language with video
content to be able to deliver results so
when you can show up on video in your
marketing this allows you to build trust
with people because people can see your
energy and they can feel your energy and
there's actually an energy transfer that
actually goes on and that's that's
something that's really really cool
about video content this is why we can
watch movies and feel something when we
watch a movie the same thing happens
through YouTube the same thing happens
through a a a free class or a webinar or
a training or in a coaching environment
and so what you want to do is you want
to pre- demonstrate to people this is
the
key you want to pre- demonstrate to
people that you can actually deliver on
those results okay and so this comes
from the words that you say how you say
it and how you structure language to be
able to get people to make an informed
decision but a decision that also feels
really good because one of the number
one mistakes that coaches and mentors we
make is that we lead with just the logic
side of things you could almost see this
as a left brain right brain as far as it
goes I don't know which one's left or
right I'm not I'm not a neuroscientist
but one of those is deals with feeling
and emotions and creativity and
vision that's what we lead with with the
marketing is we tap right into the
emotional side of people's thinking
brain but before people exchange
finances it has to make sense to their
logical mind and when we can merge those
two things together and you build trust
with people in you your product your
company they will want to buy whatever
it is that you have to offer as a coach
or Mentor now one of the biggest
mistakes that I notice that people make
when they are marketing is they over
complicate this process what I would
encourage to do is to simplify it they
over complicate the the visual aspects
of it they over complicate the technical
aspects of it and every time that I meet
a lot of coaches and mentors I meet
people that I work with that don't have
a lot of tech skill they're they're not
Savvy in a lot of this and I tell them
simplify it black and white text take a
photo of you keep it simple don't
overwhelm yourself with all this work
that you have to do trying to look like
the next
Guru that's out there that's one of the
biggest mistakes that I see that people
make is that they're trying to appear on
the outward like the guru down the
street that they met can I tell you this
my business never made money trying to
look like somebody that I wasn't and it
always made money when I just showed up
authentically as
myself and the people that I was meant
to work with love me they love listening
to me they love communicating and
connecting with me and for those that
don't bye-bye I don't need you in my
life respectfully you can go work with
another coach as far as that goes and
that's a good thing because when you
show up authentically and you tap right
into those feelings and emotions and
desires and you can learn to communicate
in a way that people truly feel seen and
heard that's the key because that
creates a feeling and sense of safety
that creates a sense of I'm in the right
place at the right time with the right
people that can help me get the results
that I want and that's where trust
becomes delivered and so again that
shows up with people in how we
communicate our body language it shows
up in the words that we write down and
it shows up in the words that we say our
facial expressions and our tone of voice
so when we bring all of these together
in our sales and marketing and and and
and I'll tell you this for years I
struggled with this I dealt with uh
negative thoughts and beliefs and I
didn't feel confident even though I had
delivered results you might say Jeremiah
you have all this track record why would
you feel that way I'm going to give you
a little bit more of a my background
here is that I actually got
started not being the person that you
see here today I got started being
somebody that worked and helped with the
video editing and then I built skills in
the marketing and then the advertising
but I couldn't show up on camera to save
my life I could be the behind the scenes
guy that was helping as the right hand
of CEOs and mentors and coaches and and
my strategies have created tens of
millions of dollars for the companies
that I've built and the clients that
I've worked with and then I learned how
to coach people really well to deliver
results our clients I've mentored and
coached thousands of
clients I was able to actually coach
alongside mentors that had built
followings so I was able to come into
those businesses and Coach people but
when it came to me putting my own
business out there can I tell you this I
actually struggled for a long time to
attract clients because I didn't
understand this
piece I didn't understand that how I
make people feel was actually one of the
number one things that I was missing and
I had a gifting to actually make people
feel incredible but I was using it to
self-protect I was using it to not show
up in my best ability
and when I
learned that you know what there's a
there's there's actually an ability that
we can all learn there's a skill set
that I think we all have and when the
rubber meets the road when we start to
get out of our head and we get out of
self- protection and we actually learn
to calm our nervous system down as well
that's one of the keys that I tell
people when I coach them is calming the
nervous system down that's actually
where confidence starts to come out
because often times when we're in fight
ORF flight or self-protective state of
mind it shows on our face it shows in
our body language we're closed off and
what that does is it's a micro
expression that people out there in the
public read as one thing it's very
interesting you could be S super
trustworthy like I was and am super
delivering results like I am super
incredible at getting people results and
yet you can show up as untrustworthy
because of how you're communicating how
you're connecting or lack of connection
as far as that goes or the things that
you're saying or what you're not saying
and I remember I would get on calls with
people and I would be like I can deliver
these results for you people would be
like there's no way you can and I'm like
what do you mean and I would start
defending myself and getting defensive
and fearful and worried and now I'm like
what do they mean and it's because I was
replaying stories that actually came
through from past experiences that I was
trying to avoid feeling anxious and this
became a battle constantly every single
day where I couldn't show up as my best
self when I finally realized that the
root was actually just inside of me and
that I could actually show up with
confidence with belief with
conviction knowing that I can help
people that started to build my business
and we were able to scale this current
business that I have to be a seven
figure company it's amazing
okay now how do you actually know that
you can deliver results where does that
come from well I believe that we all
have results that we can deliver to our
clients okay and some of you might be
watching this saying Jeremiah you still
haven't told me how to get clients
though okay I've given you the
foundations I'm building up to this
right now there's about three layers to
this that we like to do so number one
when it comes
to getting clients we have the
foundation of leading with the desire
step number two is that we can actually
deliver on the results I'm going to talk
about this next and then step number
three is where cash is exchanged and you
get a new client and there's a process
to doing this that I'm going to break
down for you at the end of this training
okay so stick with me as we go through
these three stages right here we have
the desire that we lead with with the
marketing we validate the results and
then we go to get the client so to
deliver the results you pull from your
experience as well as you can learn new
skills on things that you don't know
already so one of the things that I want
to tell you is this is that as a coach
and as a mentor there is a process and a
skill set to coaching well to being able
to listen to people and to show up
excellently I work with people that are
either brand new coaches and I Mentor
them in my program on how to do that by
the way if you're wondering about that
we have the client growth accelerator
program where I work with people every
single week to help them get results in
their business and I'd love to work with
you as well to help you get the results
that you want in your business you can
find the link below in the description
of this and so the way that you can
deliver results to people and so that
you know that you can deliver results is
this number one release the need to get
everybody
results that might sound like an
oxymoron it's not let me explain because
you can actually attract all the right
clients but at the end of the day the
responsibility of getting results doing
the work actually falls on your
clients and the truth is is that you can
do all the right things trust me I've
done it you can walk somebody through
every stage of coaching them through in
their business and they can still choose
to not grow they can still choose to not
have a growth mindset and to fight it
now one of the things that we like to do
to make sure that we're actually getting
more clients is is to pre-qualify those
that we actually notice that they
probably are more than likely not going
to get results so what we try to do is
try to pre-qualify out the people that
are actually not going to get results
and what ends up happening is is that it
works better in our favor to attract
those that are our clients one of the
biggest mistakes people make is that
they think that I have to hold on to all
of these possible clients and I need to
uh you know never lose a possible
connection with somebody or or Miss an
opportunity and that couldn't be further
from the truth when you show up in
confidence and you actually learn how to
communicate what you can do and what you
can't do and you start to get really
really clear on that with
people it will save your time save you
money and actually attract true clients
to you if you're trying to be a
generalist to help everybody that's out
there you're going to go mentally stir
crazy because you're not going to be
able to serve everybody in in all these
different ways you're not the savior of
the world you're not Jesus
okay you want to find where is your
superpower and then lean in with people
that want to know how to solve that
superpower and then what we do to
actually get clients is we just find
people that are looking to solve the
problem that we know that we can deliver
on chances are you have experience in
your life of what you've been able to do
or accomplish and if you get out out of
the fight ORF flight or the anxiety or
the nervousness of I don't know if I can
actually do this or not it starts to
reveal to you that maybe you actually
have more skill set than you realize and
I can tell you and guarantee you you
actually do have more skill set than you
realize because after working with
thousands of people over the years most
people that I meet actually have way
more skill set than they even think they
realize but they just don't know how to
communicate it in a way that connects
with clients and so when you can
actually learn just a few simple
strategies that I Mentor people on in
our coaching program that can get those
clients in front of you and then how do
you actually deliver those results to
people it starts to come together and
converge for you to where you can
actually feel confident in what you're
selling you actually feel excited that
you can deliver on the things that
people actually want and that starts to
pay you money so the process that we
look for to actually get people to pay
us money is we first have to understand
what is the desire and what result do we
deliver okay then what we get to do is
we show up by showing up in front of the
right people at the right time with the
right message based on the desire that
they have and the end result that we can
deliver and we communicate that with
them and so we communicate again with
our non-verbal communication with our
spoken word with our written words and
all of those things start to come
together in our sales and marketing CR
process okay so the sales and marketing
process that I recommend is based on a
three-step strategy that we break down
in one of our programs called the total
sixf figure online blueprint inside of
my client growth accelerator coaching
program that breaks down these three
stages you want to find the right
people you want to
promote an offer to those people and
then and this is the big one you want to
close the sale this this is where money
is exchanged and so what I noticed is
that a lot of people get stuck in this
they're trying to figure out where to
find people stage it's very simple the
best place to look is where are the
people that you want to work with where
are they spending their time and when I
talk about where it's not physically but
it could also be digitally is it on
YouTube is it on Instagram is it on
Facebook is it on LinkedIn is it on X is
it in person is it churches is it on
podcasts and so you figure out where is
the platform overall that people spend
time and then you figure out how do I
get more in front of those people so
that helps us find the people and then
as we get in front of those people
that's us promoting what we have to
offer that's us promoting that we can
deliver the result we are
self-promoting the result that we want
to deliver if you are a coach if you are
you're a mentor learning the art of
putting yourself out there and
self-promoting in a positive way not in
a way that's narcissistic or ego-driven
but that's simply telling people the
good news and the good ideas that you
have to offer in a way that builds trust
with them so you show up and you promote
that result that you can deliver to
people and we can do this through social
media we can do this through podcasts we
can do this through uh affiliate
marketing there's a lot of different
avenues that we Mentor you on inside of
my client growth accelerator to be able
to do that then and this is where the
rubber meets the road once you get in
front of the right people you close the
sale I want to tell you a story about
one of my first Consulting clients that
I worked with I actually got into a
boardroom with six people and I got
invited into that boardroom through a
referral connection that somebody gave
me and I was able to sell them in 30
minutes through a presentation that I
gave very
simply that I could deliver the results
that they desired they were a university
that I was working with and I worked
with them for a couple of years we
delivered a 30% increase in students
after 10 years of a consistent decline
in student
enrollments and I found that what I had
done for 21 years translated to
universities just as it did with with
mentorship programs or memberships or
courses or classes or coaching programs
and so but what I did was I had to
actually show up in front of the
decision
makers and get them to decide to want to
work with me by the way they were
Fielding 30 other consulting firms at
the time and I showed up and I was the
one that they they felt they literally
said this that I could deliver the
results on and guess what I did and I
and and and I got Rave Praises from the
staff members on what we were able to
actually deliver during that time with
them and so I closed the deal by being
confident by promising a result by
owning the outcome and then showing up
and
delivering and I did that all in about a
30 minute type of a presentation so
anytime that you show up with your
clients you want to be presenting
something to them that you can deliver a
result on people buy because they feel
like it's going to produce the result
and then they make the decision based on
their logical mind that the information
that they're looking for is actually
there okay and so we use online
marketing strategies to be able to do
this one of the best ways that I like to
do it is that you have some sort of a
video class or a micro recording or a
training of some kind that can be
anywhere from 30 minutes upwards to an
hour to 2 hours long just depends on how
much information you need to give people
to make a
decision and that is what helps them to
be able to decide to work with you now
if you don't feel confident delivering
in that format that's exactly what I
love to work with people with in our
client growth accelerator program and I
keep mentioning that throughout this and
if you're watching this video make sure
that you subscribe to my YouTube channel
I'd love to work with you to help you
get results we teach methods and
Frameworks all the time on this Channel
but if you want to dive deeper and
actually work with me to create it all
with you to come alongside you and
actually get you those results jump into
my accelerator program and if there's a
waiting list get on the waiting list now
you won't regret it it'll be the best
decision you ever made now I'm excited
because what we help people do is we
help them communicate in a way that
actually gets people to take action when
you can learn what are the words that
you say that actually get people to take
action what is the process of doing so
we have what we call a reverse webinar
framework and I've developed this over
the last 21 years of working with people
and it's one of the simplest most
ethical trauma informed by the way way
of doing this because it creates safety
in the conversation and it's not like a
traditional webinar or sales pitch
because it's not just a bunch of
testimonies and case studies but it
actually delivers results and
demonstrates to people that they're
going to get the outcome that they
desire and so when you can do this and
you can communicate in a
way that gets people to buy into the
thing that you say that you're going to
deliver they will purchase it and then
you can deliver those
results you can start to show up with
them and if you're somebody that says I
want to be able to learn how to do that
again subscribe to this YouTube channel
but also jump into my client growth
accelerator and I'd love to work with
you further to help you create this in
your business This is Jeremiah Kowski
signing off we'll talk soon have a good
one